Hello, I am Jayden, the founder of Clover Chalk Fashion. Nice to meet you.
In fact, there are the most Chinese users in the world who use MD.
It is an honor to have this talk in this place.
Today, I will explain how we have developed MD by interacting with users like you.
And what direction we will develop MD in the future.
In fact, there are the most Chinese users in the world who use MD.
It is an honor to have this talk in this place.
Today, I will explain how we have developed MD by interacting with users like you.
First of all, I will explain how we started.
I studied the real-time costume simulation.
It was around 2006.
As you can see in the picture, the real-time costume simulation is possible.
And the real-time costume editing is also possible.
What you see now is the video.
This is the real-time simulation that Jayden developed in 2006.
At that time, you can edit the costume version.
So I thought about what to do with this after graduation.
I decided to start a company very easily.
The biggest reason is that I used this simple software in class.
I saw students enjoying using it.
It was the happiest moment for me.
So I decided to do it better.
When Jayden graduated, he decided to start his own business.
Why did he make such a decision?
Because this software was used by students in school.
He saw that students were very interested in the process of using it.
So he was very happy to see this scene.
He was very happy.
So he decided to do this product well.
I started my business in 2009.
And I started to make products.
The first version of Marvelous Designer was released in 2010.
So you started your business in 2009.
And you started to develop products.
As you can see, this is the first version of Marvelous Designer that we released in 2010.
If you look at Marvelous Designer at the bottom,
you can make clothes with 10 different tools.
In fact, there are only 10 tools,
but you can make draping, pattern, and sewing.
So the reaction of the CG team was very hot.
As you can see, there were only about 10 tools in that version.
But even with these 10 tools,
you can make basic versions.
And you can also make clothes.
And you can make clothes.
So the reaction was very popular in the CG industry at that time.
That was the only reason.
At that time, in 2010,
we had to use a very professional tool to make clothes.
We had to use a very professional tool to make clothes.
But with our tool,
if you design patterns like this
and press the simulation button,
the production was very realistic.
So many people liked it.
From 2011, we started to use MarkDesigner in D&D, and after that, we started to use MarkDesigner in many other projects.
In 2013, 2014, and 2015, we focused on improving usability, such as freezing, deactivating, strengthening, and tech.
Thanks to this tool, we were able to create a very creative image.
Yes.
In 2013, 2014, we focused on developing tools such as freezing, deactivating, and tech.
Thanks to these tools, we were able to create a more convenient image.
As users got more familiar with the tools, they started to have more accurate and realistic ideas about how to make their own clothes.
They started to have more accurate and realistic ideas about how to make their own clothes.
They started to CAD well, seeing classic clothes that fit тресс pattern in fine detail, and modeling the entire security of design patterns in 15 to 20 years.
In fact, I think that I did much more good in KTO than when I was learning about your clothes.
I was more interested in graphic textures when I was growing up.
I've learned positive things about my style.
So, we have developed a lot of functions, such as LED paneling.
In addition, there are functions such as
These functions are used to make our model more realistic and realistic.
Thanks to this development, it has become almost perfect as a modeling tool for creating creative or very sophisticated outfits.
What the users asked for more is
Other than modeling, there are things that couldn't be done in MD.
Such as utopology, rigging, and animation.
In addition, the outfits made by our tool
The outfits made by our tool
There are a lot of images that we want to integrate with Lego tools.
After the implementation of MD, there are some new needs for the users.
They want to connect with other external software.
Such as animation, defense, topography, and UV display.
We have made a lot of improvements in this area.
In this way, the technology has improved.
At the same time, a lot of users have continued to increase.
In fact, China has the largest market of users.
In this market, we are growing the product by receiving feedback from various media, such as Weibo and various channels.
Because of the large number of uses, MD can continue to grow as it is now.
We have achieved this achievement.
We have received the Science and Technology Award at the Academy Awards last year.
This is based on everyone's recognition of our product.
So last year we won the Oscar for Technology and Technology Award.
Yes, this is based on everyone's recognition of our product.
Yes, now we will talk about how to develop the future development direction of MD.
Actually, our thought, our direction is important.
After all, as we have done so far,
Your feedback will have a big impact on the development direction.
We do a lot of surveys here.
We receive feedback through surveys, WeChat, and other channels.
And today's user summit is a great opportunity to receive feedback from you.
With this feedback, we decided on the next four development directions.
The first is all-in-one.
Not only modeling, but also animation, reading, and topology will be implemented in our tool.
The second is, as you know,
we are continuing to improve the usability of our tool.
Simulation speed, trip simulation, and various speed of work.
These are the directions of UX.
So, in terms of all-in-one, we hope that in the process of clothing modeling,
we can do it as much as possible without using other tools,
so that we don't have to run around with more software.
So, we have developed a tool that can perform various effects,
such as animation function and four-sided network grid.
The second development direction is simple and intuitive.
We will continue to improve the usability of our software.
The third development direction is to find and use assets well.
Clothes are actually not made up of patterns,
but are made up of materials such as fabric, buttons, and so on.
So, there is a development direction to find and use these materials easily.
The third development direction is,
to provide a rich number of materials.
Because a piece of clothing is not only made up of patterns,
it also needs fabric, buttons, and so on.
So, we provide various types of content in our mall,
and our clothing production can become more efficient.
Lastly, in terms of the Simulink workflow,
we promise to deliver the results of our well-made,
well-designed results to the outside world.
The fourth development direction is,
to improve the durability of our external tools.
In other words,
we can make it easier to access other P3 models
that are well-made in our mall.
First of all, I would like to explain the recent functions
and future development functions of All-in-One.
First of all, the animation editor,
that is, keyframe animation.
As you can see in the video,
we can animate the color of the material.
Not only the material,
but also the wind, gravity,
and other simulation properties can be animated.
And also,
the motion of the avatar,
the joint,
and the pose of the avatar
can be set as keyframes.
In this way,
we aim to emulate almost all the various properties
in the keyframe animation.
So, our direction is to control all the properties
through keyframes,
so that you can create more free animation.
Next is the function that makes QuadMesh well.
In fact,
QuadMesh was introduced a long time ago.
The result was not that successful,
but recently,
we have been able to make QuadMesh
without any problems.
In this way,
we can make QuadMesh very well automatically.
Compared to the 2024 version,
the results of the next version
will be very good.
So,
there is no need to create
retopology quad in the external tool.
And,
in order to use our costume well in the game,
we have to rig the costume.
Recently,
we have developed a feature
that automatically rigs the costume.
This is the result of automatic rigging.
Sometimes,
automatic rigging does not work well.
So,
we need to add some automatic rigging.
we will continue to update
the functions of automatic rigging.
And,
this is also a feature
that users have been asking for
for a long time.
In addition to the function
that controls the thickness of the mesh,
when making UV maps,
the side and back mesh
are included in the UV map.
So,
the UV map is no longer
available in Blender
or other external tools.
There is another feature
that users have been asking for for a long time.
It is the control of thickness.
In this case,
we can control the thickness of the mesh
and the UV of the mesh
in a precise way.
The original work
needs to be done in Blender.
Now,
we can make it in MAMU.
When making game contents,
we need to make sure that
the avatar's empty space is not visible.
So,
we need to make sure that
the clothes are open.
We need to make sure that
We also need to make sure
that the eyes are open.
To make the eyes open,
we need to make sure that
the eyes are opened.
We need to make sure that
the eyes are closed.
This is a feature
that automatically makes this function
work.
When making games,
in order to not see
the empty models,
such as the sleeves
or the shoes,
we need to make a space
in the air.
This work
can also be done
in the MAMU design.
In this way,
we can make game contents
in the MAMU design
by making a hole
in the UV map
This makes it possible for us to create the design perfectly within Marvelous Designer.
The next step is to enhance the usability and efficiency of our Marvelous Designer.
The most important thing is to improve the speed of draping, as shown in this video.
Recently, the stability and speed of GPU simulation have improved significantly.
Now, we are showing the same results as GPU simulation.
It will be much more convenient for you to work with the default GPU simulation mode.
Trim and Rigidbody simulation have been added to the tracking feature.
In addition, the simulation technology that can be tiered according to the test specified by the user will probably be added in the future.
In order to improve the usability and efficiency of our Marvelous Designer, we used to have the function of holding and dragging only one vertex.
Now, we have the function of holding and dragging a wide area.
In the past, we could only adjust the clothing by holding and dragging one point on the clothes.
Now, we have developed the software-based range of selection, which allows us to organize clothes in a larger area.
From now on, if you watch the video, you will be able to easily choose a wide area, which was difficult to do a little while ago.
As you can see in the screen, it can set the range of selection of the area it wants to adjust.
In addition, the UI speed has been improved a lot compared to the previous version.
In fact, the UI speed has been improved a lot compared to the previous version.
Although this is not a functional aspect,
we can make a comparison between the current version and the latest version.
As you can see, the left side is the next version, and the right side is the last version.
The last version is still working, and the next version is already finished.
As you can see, the left side is the latest version, and the right side is the current version.
You can see that there is a clear difference in the speed of their synchronization.
In the new version, the speed of operation will be increased by two to three times.
In addition, we are constantly developing the Python API to make it very easy to do repetitive work.
In order to save time, we are constantly adding Python API scripts.
In this video, we will export all the normal maps in the folder through the Python API,
and we will show you how to export the front-facing thumbnails.
The most important thing in our direction is to find and utilize the assets needed to make clothes easily.
As you know, we are running a store called Connect, and there are a lot of paid items on it.
As you know, we have a digital shopping mall called Connect, and there are a lot of digital materials in it.
In order to make it easier for you to access and download the items in the store, we have improved the library.
There are a lot of assets, so I think it would be good to access and use them easily.
If you are interested, you can use a lot of resources in this store.
In order to make it easier for you to access and download the items in the store, we have improved the library.
In the next version, we will improve the modular design function and make blocks and modular designs very easily.
In order to help you manage your digital assets better and create your own block design,
we will make major improvements to the block design in the next version.
In order to make it easier for you to access and download the items in the store, we have improved the library.
We have already needed a lot of steps to call the motion in the avatar.
But through the next function, the automatic icon mapping function, any motion can be easily applied to any avatar.
In the original version, if we want to import an external action into the model, it requires a lot of steps.
In the next version, we will use an IP mapping function to easily apply any action to any virtual model.
And we have used the power to model and render, and we can export this to the USB format.
In addition, you can directly see the effect of the hair in the 3D window, and you can direct the effect to the USB format.
Finally, we will increase the compatibility with other services and other software.
The last point is about the integration and communication with external service providers and external software.
A long time ago, there was a high-end plug-in called ZBrush, but there was a problem with its usability.
In the latest version, we have greatly improved its usability.
We can easily bring the contents created by MD to ZBrush, and the contents of ZBrush can be brought to MD.
In fact, we had this difference a long time ago, but maybe it was not so convenient at that time.
So in this version, we have made a major improvement to this part.
We can transfer the content we made in the model to ZBrush, and we can also transfer the modified content in ZBrush back to the model.
In addition, we have greatly enhanced the support of the USB format.
We can also transfer the animation function, avatar animation function, and costume simulation data to the USB format.
In terms of the USB format, we have also made a major improvement.
We have recently added virtual model animation and clothing simulation data to the compatible data.
So the compatibility with tools such as Unreal has been enhanced, and the LiveSync we provide has also become more powerful thanks to the USB compatibility.
In this way, the interaction between Unreal and ZBrush will be very good, and the addition of LiveSync will also show a stronger function based on this function.
Thanks to the development of this technology,
we can easily use our costume content directly in games based on a lot of connections.
Lastly, I would like to talk about Linux support.
In fact, among the company users, the request for Linux support has been very long.
So finally, we are going to start supporting the Red Hat Enterprise Linux version with ROCKY this year.
The last point I would like to talk about is that we are planning to support the Linux version this year.
Because a lot of enterprise users are in great demand for the Linux version,
we will finally be able to provide some MD in the ROCKY and Red Hat Enterprise Linux systems from this year.
In addition, we have prepared a lot of details about how to use the functions and more detailed functions in the afternoon session.
Please look forward to it.
If you have any questions or want to learn more about the new features,
we will have a detailed introduction in the afternoon session, and we will also have a position at the end of the session.
You can communicate with the technical staff there.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.